http://www.vet.upenn.edu/home/privacy-policy

Penn Vet | Privacy Policy
UPENN
AboutPenn Vet COVID-19 InformationWho We AreWhat We DoDiversity at Penn VetCampusesOur HistoryPress RoomEventsMaps & DirectionsEducationVMD AdmissionsIncoming VMD StudentsGraduate ProgramsDual Degree ProgramsContinuing EducationClinical TrainingResearch TrainingAccreditationResearchAreas of ResearchCenters, Laboratories & InitiativesClinical Trials | VCICAcademic DepartmentsCore Resources & FacilitiesNews, Events & ConferencesGivingMeet the TeamTraining the Next GenerationTransforming Clinical CareGroundbreaking ResearchHow to Support Penn VetDonors & FriendsPeopleFacultyFaculty/Clinician SearchAlumniFind a VMDContact Penn VetVet HospitalsNew Bolton Center HospitalCare for horses & livestock/farm animalsNew Bolton COVID-19 UpdatesEmergenciesClinical ServicesDiagnostic LaboratoriesFacilitiesAppointmentsGet DirectionsNews & EventsReferring VeterinariansRyan Veterinary HospitalCare for cats, dogs & other companion animalsRyan Hospital COVID19 UpdatesEmergenciesAppointmentsClinical ServicesDiagnostic LaboratoriesFacilitiesGet DirectionsAbout Ryan HospitalReferring Veterinarians
Contact
New Bolton Center
Kennett Square, PA
Emergencies & Appointments:
610-444-5800
Directions
Ryan Hospital
Philadelphia, PA
Emergencies:
215-746-8911
Appointments:
215-746-8387
Directions
facebook
twitter
instagramm
flickr
youtube
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Office of University Communications at the University of Pennsylvania provides access to services and information online in a manner that respects and protects your privacy. This statement describes our information-collection practices and explains how we use and protect your personal information.ScopeThis statement applies only to information collected by this website.What we collect and whyWe collect these types of information about you: Auto-collected information (web logs). The following information is automatically collected:  the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website, the date and time of your visit and the pages you visited on our site. This information helps us understand aggregate uses of our site, track usage trends and improve our services but only after any user-identifiable information has been removed.CookiesCookies are files that many websites transfer to users’ hard drives to enable the site to deliver personalized services or to provide persistent authentication. The information contained in a cookie typically includes information collected automatically by the web server and/or information provided voluntarily by the user.  Our website uses persistent cookies in conjunction with a third party technology partner to analyze search engine usage and web traffic patterns. This information is used in the aggregate to monitor and enhance the Penn web pages. It is not used to track the usage patterns of individual users.SecurityOur office is committed to ensuring the security of your information. We have put in place reasonable physical, technical and administrative safeguards designed to prevent unauthorized access to or use of the information collected online.Sharing your informationWe will not share your information with third parties except:as required by lawas necessary to protect the University's interestswith service providers acting on our behalf who have agreed to protect the confidentiality of the dataLinks to other websitesThis site may contain links to other websites not affiliated with our office. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites, including other University of Pennsylvania sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other sites for assurance that their practices safeguard your privacy.Changes to StatementWe reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time and will post the changes on this webpage.Office of Audit, Compliance and PrivacyGuidelines for creating website privacy statements (PDF file). Contact Penn's Privacy Office atprivacy@upenn.edu.Contact UsWe welcome suggestions and questions about our privacy statement. Please send them toinfopr@vet.upenn.edu. If you have questions about privacy at Penn overall, please send email toprivacy@pobox.upenn.edu or call 1-888-BEN-TIPS (1-888-236-8477).
Resources
Apply to Penn Vet
Maps & Directions
Contact Penn Vet
Accreditation
Penn Vet Library
Staff Portal
Emergency Information
University of Pennsylvania, School of Veterinary Medicine 3800 Spruce Street - Philadelphia, PA 19104
